[
  {
    "question": "Jupiter has __________ number of moons.",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "45",
      "67"
    ],
    "correct": "67"
  },
  {
    "question": "The storm on the surface of Jupiter that has been raging for 186 years is called ___.",
    "options": [
      "The Big Red Spot",
      "The Great Red Spot",
      "The Giant Red Spot"
    ],
    "correct": "The Great Red Spot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not one of Jupiter’s moons?",
    "options": [
      "Miranda",
      "Ganymede",
      "Io"
    ],
    "correct": "Miranda"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the temperature on the surface of Jupiter?",
    "options": [
      "-140C",
      "-148C",
      "-142C"
    ],
    "correct": "-148C"
  },
  {
    "question": "The red spot takes _________ number of Earth days to complete one rotation.",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter was first recorded by ___________.",
    "options": [
      "Assyrians",
      "William Hershel",
      "Babylonian astronomers"
    ],
    "correct": "Babylonian astronomers"
  },
  {
    "question": "The number of spacecrafts that have visited Jupiter is _________.",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate value of polar diameter of Jupiter?",
    "options": [
      "133,000-134,000 km",
      "132,000-133,000 km",
      "134,000-135,000 km"
    ],
    "correct": "133,000-134,000 km"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter’s atmosphere is made up of ___________.",
    "options": [
      "Hydrogen",
      "Helium",
      "Hydrogen and Helium"
    ],
    "correct": "Hydrogen and Helium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter orbits the Sun once every _______ Earth years.",
    "options": [
      "11.8",
      "11.3",
      "11.1"
    ],
    "correct": "11.8"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was Jupiter first recorded?",
    "options": [
      "5th century B.C.",
      "12th century B.C",
      "7th century B.C"
    ],
    "correct": "7th century B.C"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mass of Jupiter?",
    "options": [
      "10^6 kg",
      "10^40 kg",
      "10^27 kg"
    ],
    "correct": "10^27 kg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter has _________ rings.",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jupiter’s interior is made up of ____________.",
    "options": [
      "Magma and molten rock",
      "Rock, metal and hydrogen compounds",
      "Ammonia and methane"
    ],
    "correct": "Rock, metal and hydrogen compounds"
  },
  {
    "question": "The distance of the orbit of Jupiter is approximately _____________.",
    "options": [
      "778,340,000 km",
      "779,240,000 km",
      "776,740,000 km"
    ],
    "correct": "778,340,000 km"
  }
]